export const QUIZ_QUESTIONS = [
    {
        question: "1. In which Italian city can you find the Colosseum?",
        options: [
            "Venice",
            "Rome",
            "Naples",
            "Milan"
        ],
        correctAnswer: [ 'B' ],
        isMultiChoiseQuestion : false,
        isQuestionAttempted: false,
        isAnsweredCorrectly: null,
        learnerAnswers:[]
    },
    {
        question: "2. When did Salt Lake City host the Winter Olympics?",
        options: [
            "1992",
            "1998",
            "2002",
            "2008"
        ],
        correctAnswer: [ 'C' ],
        isMultiChoiseQuestion : false,
        isQuestionAttempted: false,
        isAnsweredCorrectly: null,
        learnerAnswers:[]
    },
    {
        question: "3. Which of the following countries have a Veto power in the United Nations Security Council?",
        options: [
            "USA",
            "Russia",
            "Australia",
            "Germany"
        ],
        correctAnswer: [ 'A', 'B' ],
        isMultiChoiseQuestion : true,
        isQuestionAttempted: false,
        isAnsweredCorrectly: null,
        learnerAnswers:[]
    },
    {
        question: "4. How many hours are there in a day?",
        options: [
            "48 hours",
            "24 hours",
            "12 hours",
            "6 hours"
        ],
        correctAnswer: [ 'B' ],
        isMultiChoiseQuestion : false,
        isQuestionAttempted: false,
        isAnsweredCorrectly: null,
        learnerAnswers:[]
    },
    {
        question: "5. How many days are there in a week?",
        options: [
            "7 days",
            "6 days",
            "3 days",
            "10 days"
        ],
        correctAnswer: [ 'A'],
        isMultiChoiseQuestion : false,
        isQuestionAttempted: false,
        isAnsweredCorrectly: null,
        learnerAnswers:[]
    },
    {
        question: "6. How many days are there in a year?",
        options: [
            "328 days",
            "365 days",
            "389 days",
            "49 days"
        ],
        correctAnswer: [ 'B' ],
        isMultiChoiseQuestion : false,
        isQuestionAttempted: false,
        isAnsweredCorrectly: null,
        learnerAnswers:[]
    },
    {
        question: "7. How many minutes are there in an hour?",
        options: [
            "60 minutes",
            "30 minutes",
            "15 minutes",
            "18 minutes"
        ],
        correctAnswer: [ 'A' ],
        isMultiChoiseQuestion : false,
        isQuestionAttempted: false,
        isAnsweredCorrectly: null,
        learnerAnswers:[]
    },
    {
        question: "8. Which animal is known as the king of the jungle?",
        options: [
            "The Tiger is known as the king of the jungle",
            "The Lion is known as the king of the jungle",
            "The Cheetah is known as the king of the jungle",
            "The Elephant is known as the king of the jungle"
        ],
        correctAnswer: [ 'B' ],
        isMultiChoiseQuestion : false,
        isQuestionAttempted: false,
        isAnsweredCorrectly: null,
        learnerAnswers:[]
    },
    {
        question: "9. Name the national flower of India?",
        options: [
            "Daisy",
            "Hibiscus",
            "Lotus flower",
            "Sun flower"
        ],
        correctAnswer: [ 'C' ],
        isMultiChoiseQuestion : false,
        isQuestionAttempted: false,
        isAnsweredCorrectly: null,
        learnerAnswers:[]
    },

    {
        question: "10. What is the largest continent in size?",
        options: [
            "Asia",
            "Africa",
            "Europe",
            "North America"
        ],
        correctAnswer: [ 'A' ],
        isMultiChoiseQuestion : false,
        isQuestionAttempted: false,
        isAnsweredCorrectly: null,
        learnerAnswers:[]
    },
]


